https://ovandony.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Ovando, your privacy is very important to us. The below privacy policy has been developed to offer you a better understanding of how we collect, use, communicate and disclose of your personal information:
•    Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
•    We will collect and use your personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
•    We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
•    We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
•    Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete and up-to-date.
•    We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
•    We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information be protected and maintained.
subscribe to our
Newsletter
Click here
Delivery
Our Guarantee
Privacy Policy
Terms
Space Rental
Be the first to know about design trends, upcoming events, seasonal collections and special promotions.
